buzztouch.com 2012-10-22

# buzztouch | Free iPhone and Android App Builder and Content Management System

## buzztouch Privacy Policy

* * *

**Please read this privacy policy carefully.**

**Introduction**

buzztouch takes your right to privacy seriously, and wants you to feel comfortable using this internet based (web-based) application. This privacy policy deals with personally-identifiable information (referred to as "data" below) that may be collected by this site. This policy does not apply to other entities that are not owned or controlled by the application editor, nor to persons that are not employees or agents of the application editor, or that are not under the application editor's control. 

**1\. Collection of data**

Registration of a user account is not available to the public. You are not required to provide any personal information that may identify you unless you complete the online registration process. If you choose to complete the online registration process, we do ask for your first and last name and may ask for your birthdate (to comply with the law). We also may ask for some basic contact information. It is possible that an uncontrollable circumstance may arise that prevents us from hiding contact information you provided during the registration process an administrator completed (such as, but not limited to, subsequent to a successful act of intrusion by a third party). Similiar to other web based applications, the application editor may also automatically receive general information that is contained in server log files, such as your IP address, and cookie information. Information about how advertising may be served on this applications (if it is the application editor's policy to display advertising) is set forth below. 

**2\. Use of data**

Data may be used to customize and improve your user experience while using this application. Efforts will be made to prevent your data being made available to third parties unless it's provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) your consent is obtained, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out for the sharing of data; (iii) a service provided on our application requires interaction with a third party with or is provided by a third party, such as an application service provider; (iv) pursuant to legal action or law enforcement; (v) it is found that your use of this applications violates this policy, terms of service, or other usage guidelines, or if it is deemed reasonably necessary by the applications editor to protect the application editor's legal rights and/or property; or (vi) this application is purchased by a third party, in which case that third party will be able to use the data in the same manner as set forth in this Policy. In the event you choose to use links that appear on this application to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies that appear on those sites. 

**3\. Cookies**

Like many web sites, this web application sets and uses cookies to enhance your user experience, such as retaining your personal settings. Advertisements may appear on this web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer; such cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the parties providing the advertisement. However, the parties serving the advertising do not have access to this application's cookies. These parties usually use non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to this application. 

**4\. Minors**

People aged thirteen or younger are not allowed to become registered users of this application. For more information, please contact us. 

**5\. Editing or deleting your account information**

This application provides you with the ability to edit the information in your user account that was provided during the registration process. You may request deletion of your user account by contacting us. Content or other information that you may have provided, that belongs to you, will be returned to you within 30 days upon request, this request must be made before an account is cancelled. Once an account is canclled, all data related to that account is permanently deleted and cannot be recovered. 

**6\. Changes to this privacy policy**

Changes may be made to this policy from time to time. You will be notified of substantial changes to this policy either by through the posting of a prominent announcement on the application, and/or by a message being sent users of the application. 

**7\. NO GUARANTEES**

While this privacy policy states standards for maintenance of data, and while efforts will be made to meet the said standards, buzztouch is not in a position to guarantee compliance with these standards. There may be factors beyond buzztouch's control that may result in disclosure of data. Consequently, buzztouch offers no warranties or representations as regards maintenance or nondisclosure of data. 

**8\. Contact information**

If you have any questions about this policy or this web based application, please feel free to contact us in writing at: buzztouch, 801 Lighthouse Ave Ste. 207, Monterey, CA 93940. You can also contact us by sending an electronic message (e-email) to: info@buzztouch.com
